("Strawberry Fields Forever")
♪ Let me take you down ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm going to Strawberry Fields ♪
♪ Nothing is real ♪
♪ And nothing to get hung about ♪
♪ Strawberry Fields forever ♪
♪ Living is easy with eyes closed ♪
♪ Misunderstanding all you see ♪
♪ It's getting hard to be
someone but it all works out ♪
♪ It doesn't matter much to me ♪
♪ Let me take you down ♪
♪ Cause I'm going to Strawberry Fields ♪
♪ Nothing is real ♪
♪ And nothing to get hung about ♪
♪ Strawberry Fields forever ♪
♪ No one I think is in my tree ♪
♪ I mean it must be high or low ♪
♪ That is you can't you know
tune in but it's all right ♪
♪ That is I think it's not too bad ♪
♪ Let me take you down ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm going to Strawberry Fields ♪
♪ Nothing is real ♪
♪ And nothing to get hung about ♪
♪ Strawberry Fields forever ♪
♪ Always know, sometimes think it's me ♪
♪ But you know, I know when it's a dream ♪
♪ I think a "No," I mean a "Yes" ♪
♪ But it's all wrong ♪
♪ That is, I think I disagree ♪
♪ Let me take you down ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm going to Strawberry Fields ♪
♪ Nothing is real ♪
♪ And nothing to get hung about ♪
♪ Strawberry Fields forever ♪